Paweł Duplaga

+48 780 106 771 | PawelDuplagalT@gmail.com | Wroc aw, Dolno I skie

Summary

As a Full stack Developer with 2 years of commercial experience, I am well-versed in object-oriented programming and have a good understanding of frontend technologies.

https://duplagadev.vercel.app/

https://github.com/PawelDuplaga

https://www.linkedin.com/in/pawelduplaga

Skills

C#, .NET, Next.js, React, Redux, Prisma, Selenium, HTML, CSS, SASS, Tailwind, Typescript, JavaScript, Python, Git, Microservices, REST API, Unity, SQL

Experience

Rigby | Wrocław, Dolnośląskie

Freelance Front End Developer | 08/2023 - Present

• Helped building ecommerce apps for individual clients.

Tech stack: Next.js, medusa.js, typescript, Figma

DevNet | Wrocław, Dolnośląskie

Software Engineer | 05/2022 - 08/2023

Project: Software for automatic algo energy trading on European markets:

Was assigned to a team that worked on non-algo backend part of the project. My role was :

- · Building new microservices for additional functionality.
- Backfilling database with needed data for shadow-testing.
- Adding new functionality to existing microservices.
- Improving performance of the system.

Tech stack: .NET, Python, Postgres, SQL, MongoDb, RabbitMQ, Azure, React

Sellintegro | Wrocław, Dolnośląskie

Junior C# Developer | 07/2021 - 10/2021

- Project : ERP Ecommerce integration software :
- Successfully implemented new software functionalityResolved bugs to improve system performance
- Provided premium customer service for the biggest clients.

Tech stack: .NET, ERP/Ecommerce API, Postman

Education

Wrocław University of Science and Technology

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science | 06/2022

Bachelor thesis - Evolutionary Optimization of Algorithms Controlling Non-Playable Characters in Games. (C#, Unity)

Languages

English (C1/C2)